Jacob Web Developer Graphic Designer DeBenedetto

- (602) 882-3969
- deben3@gmail.com
- Q doppl3r.com
- github.com/doppl3r
- in linkedin.com/in/debenedetto

about

I am passionate towards serving long-term solutions for all my client marketing needs.

I firmly believe that all client relationships should be founded on a selfless desire to resolve software & design problems by researching, communicating, and implementing professional solutions on time.

education

Northern Arizona University 2010 - 2014

Bachelor's Degree in Visual Communication with an Emphasis in Interactive Design

skills

Software / Architectures

HTML, CSS (+Bootstrap), PHP, JavaScript (+jQuery), Node.js, Java, C#, Ruby on Rails, GitHub, Google Analytics, WordPress

Graphic Design

UX, UI, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, InDesign, Flash/Animate, Motion Graphics, Photography

work experience

Yano Creative

Phoenix, Arizona 2014 - Present Lead Full Stack Web Developer
Web and mobile app UI / UX design
(Browser, Desktop, iOS & Android).
Served multi-million dollar clients
(Bosch, Choice Hotels, Myer Hotels,
Sabre Airline Solutions, Climatec,
Varitec Solutions, Bon Appetit
Restaurant, Creative Leather,
Alliance Beverage, Blue Square)

Doppler Indie Games

Phoenix, Arizona 2012 - Present Lead Game Design & Developer
 Android, desktop, & console game
 development (UI / UX, storyboarding,
 engine development, unit testing,
 marketing). Boxel (written in Java)
 was the most successful title with
 over 1 million downloads.

Freelance

Phoenix, Arizona 2011 - Present Front-End Web Development
Web and mobile app UI / UX design,
Brand identity, print design.

personal

Activities

Interests, hobbies, etc.

- Pastime

I enjoy camping, hiking, mountain biking, swimming, programming etc.

Goals

Plans for the future

- 5 Years Plan

I hope to find, collaborate & lead with a large team of creatives and developers that are passionate about the future of technology.